Map questionBrain = {
  "Environment": [
    {
      "question":
          "I am Jack not Jill, about that tropical chill. I bear the largest fruits in all the trees.",
      "answer": "Jack fruit"
    },
    {
      "question":
          "In rage I erupt to let magma escape. Mauna Loa is the biggest of me.",
      "answer": "Volcano "
    },
    {
      "question":
          "I am sharp and high rise rock exposure , especially on coasts and along rivers.",
      "answer": "cliff"
    },
  ],
  "Animals": [
    {
      "question":
          "The largest of my type on the earth, you believe I spit fire, yet a mere reptile. I am Varanus Komodensis.",
      "answer": "Komodo Dragon"
    },
    {
      "question":
          "With eight legs I terrorise, besides a venomous sting. Archnida skorpios, Desert aint no thang!",
      "answer": "Scorpion"
    },
    {
      "question":
          "The Spitz in the north west Poland and Germany. Zwergspitz, we're a mere toy breed !",
      "answer": "Pomeranian"
    },
  ],
  "Birds": [
    {
      "question":
          "I'm american and I sing. We assemble at night, not as batman but his enthusiastic sidekick.",
      "answer": "Robin"
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Not to boast, yet I'm intelligent , I talk and I recognise myself in a mirror. How can I not? Im a black and white corvidae.",
      "answer": "Magpie"
    },
    {
      "question":
          "You render me endangered. I'm white and flawless but Aron Chupa does not know to spell my name.",
      "answer": "Albatross "
    },
  ],
  "Electronics": [
    {
      "question":
          "Console or PC, gamer or pilot - you control better a strand, with me in you hand.",
      "answer": "Joystick"
    },
    {
      "question":
          "I am your portable world, the british call me a notebook. You use me in your lap and fold me when I stop.",
      "answer": "Laptop"
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Round and round, table and above. I swallow power to give you some cold.",
      "answer": "Electric fan"
    },
  ],
  "Things": [
    {
      "question": "Read me or write me but dont judge me by the cover.",
      "answer": "NoteBook"
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Im one of the oldest inventions. Hang me and watch me oscillate as time passes by.",
      "answer": "Wall Clock"
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Coffee or tea? I serve both. You're gonna miss me when I'm gone :)",
      "answer": "Cup"
    },
  ],
};
